<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoDebate</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>RESERVATION. a boon or a bane?</item>
        <item>Gas Cars or Electric Cars (hybrid)</item>
        <item>Was the ODD-EVEN rule the best way to reduce pollution? Wikll it work</item>
        <item>Narendra Modi or Arvind Kejriwal?</item>
        <item>Gobal Warming, is it real or imagined</item>
        <item>Zoos, the pros and cons</item>
        <item>Immigration, good for US or bad for US</item>
        <item>Prisons, Do we pamper criminals or treat them inhumane</item>
        <item>Poverty, is the Government doing enough for the prople</item>
        <item>Urban Living vs Suburb Living</item>
        <item>Do Criminals who are celebrities side step the Law Easier than Common People</item>
        <item>Hate vs Love</item>
        <item>Vegetarians vs Non-Vegetarians</item>
        <item>Are we doing enough to save our Planet?</item>
        <item>Are social networking sites effective, or are they just a sophisticated means for stalking people?</item>
        <item>Is torture justified when used for national security?</item>
        <item>Should cell phones be banned/allowed in schools?</item>
        <item>Is peer pressure harmful or beneficial to individuals to grow?</item>
        <item>Should violent video games be banned or they help children?</item>
        <item>Should the death penalty be taken away completely?</item>
        <item>Are beauty pageants a way of objectifying women?</item>
        <item>Should cigarettes be banned from the society?</item>
        <item>Is it unethical to eat meat?</item>
        <item>Is the Indian teaching system fair?</item>
        <item>Live-In Relationship.</item>
        <item>Celebrities as role models</item>
        <item>Should the concept of zoos should be nullified?</item>
        <item>Dieting.</item>
        <item>Sex Education in High School. Boon or a Bane</item>
        <item>All schools should make it a requirement to teach arts and music to their students?</item>
        <item>Problems in Technical Advancements</item>
        <item>Is human cloning justified, and should it be allowed?</item>
        <item>Has nuclear energy destroyed our society?</item>
        <item>War or destruction type toys for children</item>
        <item>Should animal dissections be banned in Biology classes?</item>
        <item>Should plastic bags be banned completely?</item>
        <item>Are humans too dependent on computers?</item>
        <item>Are security cameras act as an invasion to our privacy?</item>
        <item>Inter-caste marriages in India</item>
        <item>Open Schooling</item>
        <item>Does money motivate people more than any other factor in the workplace?</item>
        <item>Can money buy happiness?</item>
        <item>Is age an important factor in a relationships?</item>
        <item>Should school attendance be made voluntary in high school?</item>
        <item>Is the boarding school system beneficial to children?</item>
        <item>Are curfews effective in terms of keeping teens out of trouble?</item>
        <item>Will posting students’ grades on bulletin boards publicly motivate them to perform better or is it humiliating?</item>
        <item>Do school uniforms help to improve the learning environment?</item>
        <item>How far is competition necessary in regards to the learning process?</item>
        <item>Is it important for all schools/colleges to conduct mandatory drug testing on their students?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="content_desc">Image</string>
    <string name="edit_name">Edit name</string>
    <string name="host">Host</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>
    <string name="title_activity_host">Host a ChatRoom</string>
    <string name="title_activity_client">Join a ChatRoom</string>
    <string name="action_reopen">Reopen ChatRoom</string>
</resources>
